heroesandgenerals.com 2019-08-30

# Privacy policy

  1. HEROES & GENERALS® PRIVACY POLICY (2018-05-22) 
    1. This Privacy Policy is issued by Reto-Moto ApS, hereinafter referred to as "Heroes & Generals®". The Privacy Policy governs collection of personal data concerning users of Heroes & Generals® through all related websites; all iOS, Android or other system format apps; the Heroes & Generals® games software ("Software"); user surveys; and email correspondence between you and the Heroes & Generals® staff.
    2. Reto-Moto ApS is a company duly incorporated under Danish Law and registered under the CVR-no./company number 31 27 14 44. You may find more information about our registration at [www.cvr.dk](http://www.cvr.dk/) (the site is in Danish).
    3. By using the Heroes & Generals® websites, apps or Software, you consent to the Privacy Policy described in this document.
  2. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION VIA OUR WEBSITES, APPS, USER SURVEYS AND EMAIL CORRESPONDENCE 
    1. Heroes & Generals® only collects personally identifiable information submitted to us by you.
    2. This information is currently your e-mail address, name, country and the type of news you would like to receive from us. Your age is stored, if this is required by legislation, for access control purposes. In addition, the information will include all personally identifiable information that you chose to provide to us.
    3. We may collect payment information from you with the sole purpose of undertaking your payment, including your billing and/or shipping address as well as your card information. We may store this information after instruction by you with the sole purpose of allowing you to make easy and swift payments including subscription payments.
    4. We may also collect and store information about your purchases with us.
    5. Heroes & Generals® also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you.
  3. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION THROUGH THE SOFTWARE – ANTI-CHEAT MEASURES 
    1. If you are using the Software please be informed that your use of the Software may be monitored by gathering information in accordance with the following:
    2. WHEN PLAYERS CONNECT TO GAME SERVERS, CERTAIN ANTI-CHEAT TECHNOLOGIES IN THE SOFTWARE WILL ACTIVATE AND MONITOR GAME PLAY, THE GAME FILES ASSOCIATED WITH THE GAME SERVICE AND PLAYERS COMPUTER’S RAM. THESE TECHNOLOGIES DETECT CHEATING AND ANY UNAUTHORIZED THIRD-PARTY PROGRAMS RUNNING CONCURRENTLY WITH THE GAME SERVICE AND ANY MODIFICATIONS TO THE GAME SERVICE FILES ENABLING OR FACILITATING CHEATING. AN UNAUTHORIZED THIRD-PARTY PROGRAM IS ANY THIRD-PARTY PROGRAM OR FILE (SUCH AS AN "ADDON", "MOD", "HACK", "TRAINER", "AIM-BOT", "ESP" OR "CHEAT") THAT WE BELIEVE ENABLES OR FACILITATES CHEATING OF ANY TYPE, ALLOWS USERS TO MODIFY OR HACK THE GAME SERVICE INTERFACE, ENVI-RONMENT, OR EXPERIENCE IN ANY WAY NOT EXPRESSLY AUTHORIZED BY US, OR INTERCEPTS, "MINES", OR OTHERWISE COLLECTS INFORMATION FROM OR THROUGH THE GAME SERVICE. WHEN PLAYERS DISCONNECT FROM THE GAME SERVICE, THESE ANTI-CHEAT TECHNOLOGIES WILL BE AUTOMATICALLY DEACTIVATED.
    3. IF OUR ANTI-CHEAT TECHNOLOGIES SUSPECTS CHEATING, WE MAY COLLECT RELEVANT INFORMATION, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO YOUR RETO MOTO AND/OR HEROES & GENERALS® ACCOUNT NAME, DETAILS ABOUT ANY UNAUTHORIZED THIRD-PARTY PROGRAMS AND THE GAME SERVICE FILES MODIFICATION DETECTED, AND THE TIME AND DATE THE CHEATING WAS SUSPECTED TO OCCUR.
    4. IF WE DETERMINE A PLAYER HAS BEEN CHEATING, WE MAY ALSO, AT OUR DISCRETION, DECIDE TO TERMINATE THE TARGETED ACCOUNT, EITHER TEMPORARILY OR PERMANENTLY, DEPENDING ON THE OFFENSE BASED ON SUCH FACTORS AS RECURRENCES, SEVERITY OF THE CHEAT, AND IMPACT TO OTHER PLAYERS. IN ADDITION TO TERMINATION OF A PLAYER’S ACCOUNTS, LEGAL ACTION MAY BE TAKEN AGAINST PERSONS OR ENTITIES INFRINGING OUR RIGHTS.
  4. USE OF FIRST-PARTY COOKIES 
    1. The Heroes & Generals® websites use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. We also use cookies to track your use of Software, as explained in more detail in clause 3 above.
    2. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Our cookies are designed not to be able to be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
    3. We only use first-party cookies which are essential for our technical ability to deliver the service to you that you have demanded from us. For more information about how we use third-party cookies, please see the next clause.
    4. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenient feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the webserver that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Heroes & Generals® pages, or register with the Heroes & Generals® site or services, a cookie helps to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.
    5. The cookie may also provide us with information about your use of our services. This information is gathered with the purpose of optimizing the future development of the Software and of our other services.
    6. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies when visiting our website. Most web-browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Heroes & Generals® services.
    7. You can also at any point delete your cookies from your computer. If you delete our cookies you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our services.
    8. We use a combination of HTML 5 Local Storage and regular Web Cookies (no flash cookies). Cookies are our backup solution, if your browser does not support HTML 5 Local Storage (e.g. Internet Explorer 8 and older).
  5. THIRD PARTY COOKIES 
    1. We may use third party cookies for search marketing purposes, including without limitation Google Ads.
    2. We use third party cookies for monitoring your behavior, including without limitation Google Analytics.
    3. The use of third party cookies may imply the transfer of personally identifiable data to Google Inc. in the USA. The USA is currently without an adequacy decision by the EU Commission.
  6. PERSONAL INFORMATION 
    1. If you choose to submit any personal information to us (meaning information that can be identified as belonging to a specific individual) this information will be dealt with in accordance with the regulations of the applicable data protection legislation.
    2. The legal basis for our use of your personal information is, wholly or partly, your consent to the processing as specified; the fulfilment of our contract with you; compliance with legal obligations; and our legitimate purposes, including commercial interests vested in the game.
    3. Our use of your personal information for the abovementioned purposes is a requirement for our provision of the services of the game to you.
  7. HEROES & GENERALS®’ USE OF GATHERED/SUBMITTED INFORMATION 
    1. The personal information gathered may be used for 
      * the operation, developing and improving of the quality and use of our website and the Software;
      * administrative handling;
      * providing you with information about our products and services; and
      * marketing and promotional purposes;
      * and, internal purposes such as data analysis, statistics and research.
  8. USE OF YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS 
    1. We will use the e-mail address/addresses that you provide us with to send you communications about your account, service or technical announcements or other aspects of our ongoing business relations. We need to do this from time to time, and you are therefore not able to opt-out from receiving these e-mails from us.
    2. Provided that you have given your consent to us, we may further use any e-mail address that you have provided to us to contact you with offers and other promotional information. You may also be contacted via surveys to conduct research on your opinion of current services and Software or of potential new services that may be offered.
    3. Any promotional e-mail received from us will include an easy-to- use opt-out facility, in case you do not wish to receive any more such e-mails from us.
  9. DISCLOSURE OR TRANSFER OF INFORMATION 
    1. Heroes & Generals® may be required to disclose your personal information by law, judicial decision, and/or at the request of public authorities. Heroes & Generals® may also disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that disclosure is allowed under applicable law and is necessary to: (a) comply with legal process served on Heroes & Generals®; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Heroes & Generals®; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Heroes & Generals®, the Software, or the public.
    2. In the event that Heroes & Generals® is required to disclose your personal information cf. clause 9.1, first sentence, you will be informed hereof as soon as possible and, if possible, before the disclosure takes place.
    3. Heroes & Generals® may always also disclose your personal information with your consent or at your direction.
    4. Heroes & Generals® may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.
  10. SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 
    1. Heroes & Generals® takes reasonable measures to help secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure in accordance with generally accepted principles for the storage of personal data.
  11. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY 
    1. Heroes & Generals® will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the homepages of our websites or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access our websites to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.
  12. CONTACT INFORMATION 
    1. Heroes & Generals® welcomes your comments on our Privacy Policy. If you have comments or believe that Heroes & Generals® has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact Heroes & Generals® at support.heroesandgenerals.com.
  13. RIGHT TO KNOW ABOUT OUR PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA 
    1. Under applicable law, you may have the right of access to and the right to have the data relating to you rectified. If you want to exercise these rights, you can contact support.heroesandgenerals.com
    2. You also have the right to object to processing as well as the right to data portability and to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
    3. Your personal data will be stored for as long as you have an active account with us and for an additional period of [5 years].
  14. STATUTORY RIGHTS 
    1. It is of utmost importance to us that we adhere to the applicable data protection legislation requirements and that your personal information is treated in an orderly and sage manner. If, however, you are of the opinion that you have statutory rights in your jurisdiction that are binding on Heroes & Generals® and which grants you better protection, please do not hesitate to contact us at info@reto.dk.

For any questions or assistance please visit our [Support](http://support.heroesandgenerals.com/) section.
